welcome to our presentation we designed a deep convolutional net work for the segmentation of biomechanical images
歡迎來到我們的簡報。我們設計了一個深度卷積網絡，用於生物力學影像的分割
which we called unit it learns to signal images in an end-to-end setting
我們稱之為單元，它學會在端到端設置中對圖像發出信號
which means a raw image in
這意味著原始圖像在
and ready segmentation map out the
和準備好的分割圖
main challenges were that we had only around 30 annotated images per application
主要挑戰在於每個應用程式只有約 30 張註解圖片
and we
和我們
nearly always have touching objects of the same class that need to be separated by the segmentation algorithm
幾乎總是有相同類別的接觸物體需要由分割算法進行分離
here is the architecture of our unit like all other commercial
這是我們單元的架構，像所有其他商業網路一樣
networks it consists of a large number of different operations illustrated
它由大量不同的操作組成，如這些小箭頭所示
by these small arrows the input image is fed into the network here at the beginning then
輸入影像在這裡的開始處進入網路，然後
the data is propagated
資料被傳播
through the network along all possible paths and at the end the ready segmentation
通過網絡沿所有可能的路徑傳播，最終得到準備好的分割
map comes out each
地圖會顯示出來
blue box corresponds to a multi-channel feature web the xy size is denoted
藍色框對應於多通道特徵，xy 大小在此標示
here and the number of featured channels is denoted here
此處標示了特徵通道的數量
most of the operations are compilations followed
大部分操作是隨後的編譯
by a nonlinear activation function in d'italia it looks like this it is a standard 3x3 convolution
由非線性激活函數構成，在 d'italia 看起來是這樣，它是一個標準的 3x3 卷積
followed by a nonlinear
隨後是非線性
activation function an important
激活函數的一個重要
design choice is that we only use the valid part of the convolution
設計選擇是我們僅使用卷積的有效部分
which means that for a 3 by 3 convolution
這意味著對於 3x3 的卷積
a 1 pixel border is lost this allows later to process large images in individual tiles the
會丟失 1 像素邊界，這使得後來可以在單獨的瓷磚中處理大型圖像
next operation in the u net is a max pooling operation
在 U-Net 中的下一步操作是最大池化操作
it reduces the xy size of the feature map so i have illustrated
它會減少特徵圖的 XY 大小，所以我已經說明了
it as a downward
它作為一個向下的
arrow the max pooling operation acts on each channel separately it
箭頭，最大池化操作對每個通道分別作用
just propagates the maximum activation from each 2x2 window to the next feature map
它僅將每個 2x2 窗口中的最大激活值傳播到下一個特徵圖
after each max pooling operation
每次最大池化操作後
we increase the number of featured channels by a factor of 2 all
我們將特徵通道的數量增加了 2 倍
in all the sequence of convolutions
在所有的卷積序列中
and max pooling operations results in a spatial contraction
並且最大池化操作導致空間收縮
where we gradually increase the bot and at the same time decreased the where standard
我們逐漸增加底部，同時減少標準
classification every ends here
分類每個結束於此
and all maps
和所有地圖
and maps all features to change single output vector the unit has an additional expansion
和映射所有特徵以改變單一輸出向量，該單元具有額外擴展
path to create a high resolution segmentation map
創建高解析度分割地圖的路徑
this expansion path consists of a sequence of up convolutions
這個擴展路徑由一系列向上卷積組成
and concatenation with the corresponding high resolution features from the contracting path this convolution uses
並與收縮路徑中對應的高解析度特徵進行串接，這個卷積使用
a learned kernel to map each feature vector to the 2x2 pixel output window again
一個學習到的核來將每個特徵向量映射到 2x2 像素輸出窗口
followed by a nonlinear activation function that's
隨後是非線性激活函數
it the output segmentation map has two channels one for foreground
輸出的分割圖有兩個通道，一個用於前景
and one for the background class due to the unfettered convolutions
和一個用於背景類別，這是由於自由卷積
this map is smaller than the input image the segmentation of the yellow area uses
這張地圖比輸入影像小，黃色區域的分割使用了
the input data of the blue area with
藍色區域的輸入數據與
a novel uptight strategy
一種全新的嚴格策略
we can segment arbitrarily large images at
我們可以隨意分割超大圖像
the border we extrapolate
在邊界處我們外推
the data by mirroring
透過鏡像來處理數據
the main challenge in biomedical
生物醫學領域中的主要挑戰
image segmentation is a low number of training data to teach
影像分割中的訓練數據量少，難以教學
the network the desired robustness properties
網絡所需的穩健性特徵
we apply random elastic deformations
我們應用隨機彈性變形
the resulting deformed image looks perfectly like an original image
變形後的圖像看起來與原始圖像完全一致
if i remove the green red lines here the deform cells cannot be distinguished
如果我移除這裡的綠色紅色線條，變形細胞將無法與真實細胞區分
anymore from real cells
無法再與真實細胞區分
the second challenge are touching objects of the same class that have to be correctly separated here
第二個挑戰是相同類別的觸碰物體必須在這裡正確分隔
we insert background pixels between all touching objects
我們在所有接觸的物體之間插入背景像素
and assign an individual loss weight to every pixel this
並為每個像素分配單獨的損失權重
allows a strong panel utilization if the network accidentally
如果網絡意外地
closes these gaps we
關閉這些間隙
train the unit for the segmentation of neuronal structures
我們訓練單位以進行神經結構的分割
and electron microscopy the challenges in this dataset are structures with very low contrast
在電子顯微鏡下，這個數據集中的挑戰是對比度非常低的結構
fuzzy membranes
模糊膜
and
和
other cell compartments
其他細胞區室
we
我們
achieved a new best score in terms of the warping error which
在變形錯誤方面達到了新的最佳分數
was most better than
比較好
from a sliding window convolutional neural network furthermore
來自滑動窗口卷積神經網絡進一步
our net break is very fast training
我們的網絡中斷速度非常快的訓練
time was only 10 hours and the application is about 1 second per image
時間只有 10 小時，應用程式每張影像約 1 秒
we
我們
also participated at the sp cell tracking challenge 2015
我們也參加了 SP Cell Tracking Challenge 2015
one of the data sets contains cells and phase contrast microscopy they
一組數據集包含細胞和相位差顯微鏡，他們
show strong shape variations weak outer borders
顯示出強烈的形狀變化，外部邊界較弱
and strong irrelevant inner borders
和強烈的無關內部邊界
and the cytoplasm has the same structure like the background the
細胞質的結構與背景相同
output of the unit is shown syan here and the ground throughs in yellow we
單元的輸出顯示在此，地面透過黃色顯示
won on this data set with intersection of a union of 92% while
在這個數據集上，交集聯集的結果為 92%
the second best method only reached 83%
第二好的方法僅達到 83%
another dataset was even more challenging it contains touching in overlapping cells partially invisible borders
另一個數據集甚至更具挑戰性，它包含重疊的單元格、部分不可見的邊界
and the cells leaves the focal plane here we want with an even larger margin more details
單元格離開了焦平面，我們希望有更大的邊距和更多的細節
and the implementation are available on our home page thank you for your attention
實施方案已在我們的首頁提供，感謝您的關注